

SUMMARY

A motivated and open minded developer who loves to develop an impactful solution for any business or non-business needs. I tend to make use of modern web technologies to build web apps that looks great, feels fantastic and functions correctly. My goal is to build products that provide pixel perfect, performant experiences.

Pramesh Karki

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+977-9842473580 prameshkarki0407@gmail.com www.karkipramesh.com.np New Baneshwar, Kathmandu Nepal

EDUCATION

Nepal College of Information Technology 2018-Running

Balkumari, Lalitpur, Nepal Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering

Vishwa Adarsha Higher Secondary School 2016-2018 Itahari Sunsari, Nepal Computer Science

EXPERIENCE

Cliffbyte Pvt.Ltd

Full stack developer/2021 - Present

As a freelancer

Full Stack Developer / 2019 - 2021

SKILLS

Docker
React.js
Node.js (Express Js)
MongoDB, SQL, MySQL
GraphQL,Redis, Typescript

HOBBIES

Designing
Trekking
Reading books
Volunteering